{
    "subject": "resource/The_Carpet_Frogs",
    "predicate": "property/origin",
    "object": "resource/Canada",
    "human_readable": "The Carpet Frogs originated from Canada.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9738234877586365,
            "question": "Are Carpet Frogs native to Canada?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8758177757263184,
            "question": "Where did the Carpet Frogs originate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8283115029335022,
            "question": "What is a unique characteristic of Carpet Frogs from Canada?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8264888525009155,
            "question": "What country is the origin of the Carpet Frogs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7563457489013672,
            "question": "Is Canada the home country of the Carpet Frogs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6557215452194214,
            "question": "Can you name a type of frog from Canada?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5592474937438965,
            "question": "Are Carpet Frogs from North America?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4911717176437378,
            "question": "What is another name for the Carpet Frog?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4888911247253418,
            "question": "Is Canada known for its diverse frog species?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3107224106788635,
            "question": "Where can you find Carpet Frogs in the wild?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Carpet Frogs originated from Canada.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5705_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Canada known for its diverse frog species?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5705_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is another name for the Carpet Frog?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5705_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are Carpet Frogs from North America?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5705_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5705_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5705_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5705_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5705_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5705_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5705_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5705_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5705_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5705_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5705_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents contain multiple mentions of The Carpet Frogs being a Toronto-based rock band, which implies that they originated from Canada."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents indicate that The Carpet Frogs are a Toronto-based rock band, which is in Canada. Therefore, the statement that The Carpet Frogs originated from Canada is supported by the provided context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}